Macross Frontier: Labyrinth of Time
/It's been over half a century since
humanity began its journey across the stars.
During that time, we have come into contact
with many alien races, including some
descendants of the long lost interstellar
civilization known as the Pro to culture.
Many tears have been shed because
of this, both in grief and in joy.
Hey everybody!
You all having a good time?!
I'm sorry to say this, but...
this next song will be the last one.
- Aw! We want more!
This song is for those I hold dear.
I hope you like it.
Without a doubt these feelings are within me
Unable to be contained, they overflow
When I think of you, my bosom becomes the universe,
holding the stars close
Our days are limited
It's been
some time since that fateful day.
Our days are limited
I've decided to spend them loving you
To put an end to that tragic war,
Sheryl burned what
was left of her life with a song that moved the galaxy.
Sheryl burned what was left of her life
with a song that moved the galaxy.
I'm starting to find the strength
Sheryl burned what
was left of her life with a song that moved the galaxy.
I'm starting to find the strength
To this day, she still sleeps.
to say I love you
It's a long road
Guided by the light
shining in the distance
Let us always meet again
Ranka?
...able to meet now
This feeling that grows ever deep,
Huh?! Fold Waves?!
I vow to keep
- Shush!
May it never waver
amidst the freezing wind
The Galactic Heritage Bureau has
given clearance for us to investigate.
Thanks for always
helping out, everyone.
Checking out lost technology is also
the job of Super Dimensional Tour escorts.
Plus we get to go to your concerts.
This place is really amazing though.
The Well of Souls is a temple left behind
by the descendants of the Pro to culture.
The Well of Souls...
A place to commune with the gods.
Legend says it was used to
converse with the dead as well.
Please make this quick, Ranka.
You still have new song lyrics to finish.
And we leave for your
next tour stop tomorrow.
Sorry for worrying you...
But I feel that I might
reach him this time.
Here you go. Taiyaki and
tuna buns, your favorites.
This setup looks like a
grave site every time.
Hey! Don't say that.
That's right. Alto promised
he'd come back alive, so there.
What was that?
Fold Waves!
Just as I thought. It must have
reactivated in response to
Ranka's voice during last night's concert.
It's calling me...
Huh?
It's Alto who's calling!
Wait! It's too dangerous!
This is the mysterious Labyrinth of Time,
where hidden memories are awakened
Ranka!
Why am I here? Why me?
Empty answers dance all around me
Even if it's just a dream, I don't care
If it means I can change the past,
I'd become the Devil himself
Ranka!
I still remember the day
you and I first met
- Huh?
- Alto?
it really him?
The wind felt kind of gentle that day.
No, it's just her projected memories.
I'm getting strong readings from both Ranka's brain,
(I had a feeling...)
and the Fold Bacteria in her abdomen.
And the Fold Bacteria
in her abdomen.
You felt so familiar, though we only just
met and the Fold Bacteria in her abdomen.
You felt so familiar, though we only just met
And I had a funny feeling that
maybe you felt the same way about me
From that day on, every day was so much fun
and so sad
And just a little bit lonely
I was overwhelmed by all those feelings
I was overwhelmed at the thought of your name
025-8 and SO4
Can you hear this voice of mine?
Hello, Ranka?
I want you to show me more
What is it?
It's pretty late.
About all sorts of stars
About all sorts of you
Oh, so you can't sleep.
025-8 and SO4
Well then, can
you see towards the eastern sky?
Well then, can you see
towards the eastern sky?
Is my voice reaching you?
That's right, turn off the lights.
I want you to tell me more
About all sorts of stars
About all sorts of songs
Sheryl!
Please, Alto! Respond!
Please, hurry back...
...for Sheryl!
You need to wake Sheryl!
We traveled separate paths,
but dreamed the same dream
That's why I wasn't alone
Since I lost you,
I feel your presence everywhere
The image of you, the scent of your hair
From that day on, every day was so beautiful
and so exciting
And just a little bit lonely
Because only when I'm with you
do the stars shine bright,
Whoa... Hey, everyone's watching.
The seas go deep,
And the skies reach high
021-5 and FO9
Can you hear this voice of mine?
I want you to show me more
About all sorts of stars
About all sorts of you
021-5 and FO9
Is my voice reaching you?
I want you to tell me more
About all sorts of stars
About all sorts of songs
What do you think of me now?
Have I become a stronger person?
I want you to tell me gently
When I was...
in love with God...
021-5 and FO9
I never expected...
Sheryl? Alto?!
021-5 and FO9
ls my voice reaching you?
-0271-5 and FO9
-FO9
-Is my voice reaching you?
I want you to tell me more
About all sorts of stars
So pretty...
About all sorts of you
Such a beautiful song.
Did she reach him?
I can't tell.
-When I was...
-025-8 and SO4
But the Fold Waves from the ruins are still getting stronger.
ls my voice reaching you?
-In love with God...
-I want you to tell me more
About all sorts of stars
-025-8 and SO4
-(025-8 and SO4)
Is my voice reaching you?
-025-8 and SO4
-(025-8 and SO4)
I want you to tell me more
-025-8 and SO4
-S04
-Is my voice reaching you?
I want to hold on to this feeling
Alto?
That I'm with you right now
-025-8 and SO4
-S04
-Is my voice reaching you?
-Reaching you
I want to hold on to this feeling
Alto!
That I'm with you right now
-That I'm with you right now
-(That I'm with you right now)
It's an amplified
Fold Wave transmission!
Is that... him?
At the end of the light...
I'm not losing you this time.
Shining eyes, fall into the dark side
I can't go back again
THE PATH OF RUIN
Sv-303 Standby to launch.
A world played out through this
Guide units all connected.
Spatial compression thrust amplification system nominal.
Moonlight guided melody Spatial compression
thrust amplification system nominal.
Moonlight guided melody
QFV reaction bullet set completed.
Wait to see
What's going on QUIETLY
Multidimensional Fold Quartz System synchronizing smoothly.
THE TUNE OF DESTRUCTION IS...
So don't look back
Lying in wait for a chance at revolution
Into you,
there ls no way out NOT YET
Wait for the time
of awakening quietly, quietly
Gotta be ready to rock
Maybe... Only you can, only you can
rock me
I know you can, I know you can
I know you can, I know you can Space distortion
rate increasing. Approaching Dimensional Fault.
Space distortion rate increasing.
Approaching Dimensional Fault.
Only you can, only you can
rock me
Siren System operating
within operational parameters.
To the darkness, to the darkness
Ready to rock, get ready to rock!
Good. Now, thy voice shall open
the gates to a new era,
Countdown to ruin, YES/
o' great Singer of the Dark.
Ready to rock, get ready to rock!
Unleash it now
Gonna be ready to rock
Into you
Gonna be ready to, be ready to rock!
Macross Delta: ZETTAI LIVE!!!!
For the past five decades,
Windermere has been in
constant bitter conflict
with the humans of Earth.
To us,
it was a holy war to reclaim
the freedom of our skies.
But even so, too many wings and
too many precious lives have been lost.
Let us pray that the souls of the departed
be borne by the wind to the Fountain
of Wind so that they may rest in peace.
We are currently negotiating a peace
treaty with the U.N. Government,
If I try, I can fly. If I try,
I can fly. If I try, I can fly.
- If I try—
- Fre-Fre!
Come on, loosen up.
Freyja, tense to the max.
Well, this ls her first time
back since running away
from her village, plus it's a concert
held by her king to celebrate the truce.
Get it together
or be left behind!
Alrighty!
To the Children of the Wind
united under the sacred feather,
I vow to make the winds of
peace sweep throughout the galaxy.
In the name of the Great Wind!
Upward Bomb Burst/
Up for the challenge, Crimson Knight?
Heh, you dull-winded oaf!
Go!
What?!
Feelin' good!
Whoa! He's doin'
the Immelmann dance/
Hayate, get back in formation!
Relax Mirage, the show will be
fine as long as we nail the finale—
- Damn you!
- What?/
You dare act out in the
presence of His Majesty?!
It's just a bit of service!
Your service isn't needed!
Still just a boy.
- Crimson Knight! Come back!
- Get him, Sir Bogue!
Ah... Crimson Knight's
got some moves.
Your guy's dance
isn't bad either.
See ya later, Crimson Knight!
Hey! What the...!
Music is Love!
Music is Hope!
Music is Life!
Music is Mystery!
Music is Energy!
Listen to the songs of goddesses!
Super Dimension Venus, Walkiure!
In the wandering glacier
a secret lies hidden
By a freak accident
an encounter happened. So restricting
Welling up from the depths of chaos
the deep freeze shows its 108 facets
Lips so hot
that they seem to melt
Complete meltdown, it forms
I don't know. Just repeating
this urge,
letting it out...
Pure falling snow touches my hand
as they attract each other
My feelings become aroused, so dizzy
No spare lives, you and me, to the limit
Please accept it,
this kiss, right now
See, the silver world returns
The sound of silence that glimmered faintly
Unleash all the pent-up emotions,
-Sing
Sing
! fell in love, in this infinite galaxy
These feelings spilling out of me
are so disjointed
They are instinct without malice,
so they overlap
Don't take them from me just yet
Pure falling snow touches my hand
as they attract each other
My feelings become aroused, so dizzy
No spare lives, you and me, to the limit
Please accept it,
this kiss, right now
- Walkure!
- Freyja!
- Apple Girl!
Thank you everybody!
Freyja's rune is so bright!
What a dazzling wind,
so pleasant to the rune.
I wish both Roid and Keith
were here to feel this wind.
Whew... Huh?
Freyja?
These houses are delightful.
They're so cute!
So serene. So excited.
Yeah. It's really nice, Freyja...
Hey, what's wrong?
Freyja ran off, bailed on her engagement.
Rei-Rei!
Freyja!
Mister Mayor!
I'm really, really...
I'm so totally sorry!
It's a relief to see you're okay, Freyja.
Huh?
Thank you for taking care of Freyja.
On behalf of the people of
Ravengrass Village, I bow my rune.
Mister Mayor.
No, it was Freyja's voice
that bridged the gap between
Windermere and ourselves.
- Freyja!
Welcome back!
- It's been so long.
- Rune Pika!
Alright guys, wait your turn.
M-Muah! Here you go!
Gori-Gori cute!
Ten win streak!
Heh, weak and feeble.
I'm a woman without mercy.
You've performed with Ranka Lee,
the Super Dimensional Cinderella?!
Ah, yes. I used to be a solo idol, so...
I wouldn't say you "performed with" her.
It was a variety show where
she watched a video of you
rodeo riding a Galactic Hippo
during a studio taping, that's all.
G-Galactic Hippo?
Hmm, was that what it was?
I can't really recall... Huh?!
- Wow.
- Kaname, embarrassing past.
Cut it out!
Sparkling apple cider? No thanks.
Why not? It's tasty.
All she's been drinking is apple milk.
I know! She can't handle the fizzles.
What a baby!
I gotta say, our village's
apples are Gori-Gori great!
Right, Hayate?
Yeah, Gori-Gori for sure.
Wait, are you
Freyja's boyfriend?!
Really? But isn't he an Earthling?
W-Wha...?
No, me and Hayate aren't like that...!
So what's an Earthling's wind taste like?
Wife's been talking about wanting kids.
Well, the sooner the better.
Then it's on to the second and third one.
What is it?
Oh, it's just...
Everyone here really is so young...
The average lifespan of a
Windermerian is 30 years.
Around these parts,
a child plants their own
sapling at the age of five.
Remember, the people of this planet
are very different from us.
Mister Mayor.
Thank you sir,
for welcoming Freyja home like this.
- Likewise, seeing Freyja so happ—
- Defection is a capital offense.
Be thankful for His Majesty Heinz's mercy.
Yes, I fully understand.
Why're you bringing that up?
Freyja sang to bring peace!
You have no say in this, outsider.
What did you say?!
Hey, what's with you guys?!
Back off!
Stop this nonsense!
Party's over!
What use is talking to
aliens at this point?!
We should be running them out!
By order of His Majesty,
I'm tasked to protect you.
Even though I completely
agree with those men.
- What?!
- Hold it. Let him handle this.
You're disturbing the peace.
Sir Knight!
To hell with Walkire!
They're spewing their
filthy songs in our wind!
Like it or not, they are
His Majesty's guests.
Do you mean to oppose your king?
Just a moment please.
- Father Johann?
- Father Johann!
Father Johann!
Father Johann?
Johann Winly.
One of the priests who
serve the God of the Wind.
Please, could you possibly forgive
these men for their offense?
Father Johann...
As you wish.
You have my thanks.
You three should leave for now.
W-We will.
Thank you, Father Johann.
I hope you will forgive my intrusion.
No, you really saved us.
So you are Mikumo Guynemer,
Singer of the Stars.
I am Mikumo Guynemer of Walkdure,
nothing more.
Yes, of course. Do forgive me.
Freyja Wion.
Yesterday was the first time
I've heard you sing in a while.
I remember being welcomed by your
songs every time I visited this village.
I hope you continue to add
your fine voice to the wind.
Y-You betcha!
Freyja! Where are your manners?
That's no way to talk to Father Johann!
Oh!
Oh, I missed the color of the wind here.
By the end of Spring, this place will
be blooming with apple blossoms.
Little white flowers everywhere!
I'd really like to show you, Hayate.
Yeah, I'd like to see it someday.
Where did you get an old picture like that anyway?
That's so cute. The two of them off alone in the orchard.
That's so cute. The two of
them off alone in the orchard.
I am a woman without limits. That's so cute.
The two of them off alone in the orchard.
I am a woman without limits.
Hmm?
Something else bothering you?
It's an impossible pairing,
Windermerians and Earthlings.
How can you be so certain?
My family was killed by Earthlings.
Our village has known war as
well. And there's the fact that
our life span is different
than that of Earthlings.
To tell the truth, the
villagers are all worried
that one day this will bring
sorrow to you folks and Freyja.
Even so, one day all winds will be as one.
Found it!
I'm home.
So this is your tree, Freyja?
No, it's my grandma's.
I never met her, but this tree
is the oldest one here,
with the best-tasting apples.
It's so good!
Right?
And then the smaller trees
around you are the ones I planted.
Oh.
The one atop that hill is my mom's,
and the one back there is my dad's.
My mom became one with the wind
when I was three, and my dad
just after the last war.
I see.
I think I was about ten
when my old man died.
You said he was a pilot.
I told you about Commander Arad too, right?
Yes, he was your father's subordinate.
That's right.
He recruited me to be a pilot when I
didn't know what to do with myself.
I still remember it vividly,
my first solo flight.
I felt it right then...
The feeling that I was with my dad.
He was kind of an eccentric guy.
Always sending hand written letters
from where he was stationed,
each with a single random phrase.
Like what?
Like this.
“The sky is vast."
The sky is...
The sky is vast!
"Scent of the rain."
"Stars fill the night."
A fruit still green is one
Being attracted is two
My heart is burning
Freyja...
A promise is three
Being plucked is four
Traveling the sky's end
The stars must be sad foo
"Clouds shaped like mountains."
Five, tears well up and fall
"The sea is blue."
"The desert is hot."
Missing those that are gone
“The galaxy is huge."
Let us sing a song of prayer, that it
reaches the far shores of this sea of light
Red apples, small apples
Bits of joy that ripen and change color
Let us count them one by one
to see the faces
of those we I love
That was a Windermerian song of legend,
passed down for generations.
It's about a village girl and the God of
the Wind who came from across the stars.
A bittersweet love song.
I love you, Freyja!
I want to live our lives out together!
Did you know that apple blossoms
only bloom for ten days?
They burst into bloom,
and fall right away.
Are you really okay with that?
With an apple flower like me?
I love you Freyja, however you are!
Thank you, Hayate.
I also...
What?
Shining eyes, fall into the dark side
Where's that coming from?
There's a disturbance in the wind.
Tense, so on edge, but it kinda...
I can't go back again THE PATH OF RUIN
...Sounds like Kumo-Kumo.
This singing... Is it possible?
A world played out through this
A Fold Gate?!
Windermere is isolated by a dimensional fault!
Moonlight guided melody
Folding directly
into the atmosphere isn't possible.
Wait to see
what's going on QUIETLY
THE TUNE OF DESTRUCTION IS...
So don't look back
THE TUNE OF DESTRUCTION IS... So don't look back
An unidentified ship has appeared above Ravengrass.
An unidentified ship has
appeared above Ravengrass.
Lying in wait for a chance at revolution An
unidentified ship has appeared above Ravengrass.
Lying in wait for a chance at revolution
Magnifying image!
Into you,
That's... a Ma cross class ship?!
There ls no way out NOT YET
there is no way out NOT YET
It appears to have been heavily modified.
Wait for the time of awakening
Unable to identify its origin.
Very well. Scramble the Aerial Knights
quietly, quietly
and launch the Sigur Berrentzs!
Gotta be ready to rock
Main reactor power output increasing!
Maybe... Only you can, only you can
Engaging artificial gravity!
Sigur Berrentzs taking flight!
Rock me
! know you can, I know you can
Sigur Berrentzs taking flight!
Only you can, only you can
rock me
To the darkness, to the darkness
Ready to rock, get ready to rock!
Countdown TO RUIN, YES!
Unleash it now
Gonna be ready to rock
Unknown hostile deploying fighters!
Damn invaders!
Into you
Let's go!
Gonna be ready to rock
This is the 3rd Order. Joining you now!
Gonna be ready to, be ready to rock!
Da!
Gonna be ready to, be ready to rock! Target
inbound! Unable to identify? It's an unknown fight—
Gonna be ready to, be ready to rock!
Theo!
Theo! Everyone spread out!
- Xao!
- I'm still good!
Alright then...
Gotcha!
Yeah everybody, it's showtime.
RIGHT HERE, hey go now
UNTO DESTRUCTION, LET'S Rock! Rock!
Yeah ALWAYS just be cool,
It dodged them?!
! know that maybe you're right
I'm gonna...No No No No/
I'm gonna...No No No No/ Everyone,
take shelter inside the church.
Everyone, take shelter
inside the church.
Say na na na na, what you say
Everyone, take shelter inside the church.
I'm gonna make you mine, Na!/ Na! Na! Na/
I'm gonna make you mine, Na!/ Na! Na! Na!
Can't reach either the Aether or Ragna.
I'm gonna make you mine, Na!/ Na! Na! Na/
That song is jamming all Fold communications?
That song is jamming all
Fold communications?
Are you crazy? Never let you go That
song is jamming all Fold communications?
Are you crazy? Never let you go
You got it, never know, in sacrifice
Short range comms are still working.
I'm calling in the Siggies by remote.
(Yes I know, I know)
Fold Sound Link transition on schedule.
What the hell is going on? You're right
So crazy, break it down,
break it down, break it down
Are you serious? Maybe, maybe... Of/
Just make it a reality
So crazy, crazy, get out! What do you say?
What?!
Ugh... What?
! know what you want
You're the only one, take me higher
Tell me, what's the meaning
of darkness, darkness?
No way out, let me tell you
Oh! Oh! Show me the way,
oh no way, no way out
oh no way, no way out Freyja!
Oh! Oh! Show me the way,
oh no way, no way out
oh no way, no way out Freyja!
What is this song?
It's affecting our Bio-Fold Receptors!
Incoming!
Yeah everybody, it's showtime.
RIGHT HERE, hey go now
UNTO DESTRUCTION, LET'S Rock! Rock!
Yeah ALWAYS just be cool,
! know that maybe you're right
I'm gonna...No No No No/
Say na na na na, what you say
I'm gonna make you mine, Na!/ Na! Na! Na/
Are you crazy? Never let you go
You got it, never know, in sacrifice
(Yes I know, I know)
What the hell is going on? You're right
So crazy, break it down,
break it down, break it down
So crazy, break lit down, break it down, break it down?
- The apples...! - Freyja!
Are you serious? Maybe, maybe...Oh!
The apples! Everyone's apples!
Don't!
Are you serious? Maybe, maybe...Oh!
My dad's! My mom's!
Just make it a reality
No! They can't! They can't!
So crazy, crazy, get out! What do you say?
Get a hold of yourself!
So crazy, crazy, get out! What do you say? You think
your mom and dad would be happy if you died here?!
You think your mom and dad
would be happy if you died here?!
! know what you want You think your mom
and dad would be happy if you died here?!
You think your mom and dad
would be happy if you died here?!
You're the only one, take me higher You think
your mom and dad would be happy if you died here?!
You're the only one, take me higher
Tell me, what's the meaning of darkness,
darkness? I won't let them do this.
Tell me, what's the meaning
of darkness, darkness?
No way out, let me tell you When
the sadness flowing through one's heart
When the sadness flowing
through one's heart
cuts like a knife,
Singing?
Cuts like a knife,
it leaves an open wound
Mikumo!
It leaves an open wound
it leaves an open wound
They're wavering?!
It leaves an open wound
it leaves an open wound
I see.
We have to disrupt the enemy's
Bio-Fold Waves as much as possible!
For how long have [ struggled? We have to disrupt
the enemy's Bio-Fold Waves as much as possible!
For how long have [ struggled?
Right behind you!
The exit is nowhere to be found
Don't worry about us! Go!
No time to be afraid,
Very well. Let's go!
No time to be afraid, - Oorah sir!
- Yes sir!
- Oorah sir!
Because time waits for no one - Oorah sir!
- Yes sir!
Because time waits for no one
because time waits for no one
Roger.
Because time waits for no one
because time waits for no one
Freyja...
I'll be fine. Get going!
Peel off that scab deep in your heart,
with your own bare hands
Onward to a brave new world, NEXT/
Delta Flight, follow me!
Hmm?
Onward to a brave new world, NEXT/
Misery ongoing. So... Finally started singing
eh, Walkure? Now how will you respond, Siren?
So... Finally started singing eh, Walkure?
Now how will you respond, Siren?
It still hurts like hell So... Finally started
singing eh, Walkure? Now how will you respond, Siren?
So... Finally started singing eh, Walkure?
Now how will you respond, Siren?
Biting your lips against the blasting wind (been there, done that!) So...
Finally started singing eh, Walkure? Now how will you respond, Siren?
Biting your lips against the blasting wind
(been there, done that!)
Biting your lips against the blasting wind (been there, done that!)
They attacked Freyja's village. I won't let them gel away with this!
They attacked Freyja's village.
I won't let them get away with this!
Over the limit, go for it. Pulse thumping They attacked
Freyja's village. I won't let them get away with this!
Over the limit, go for it. Pulse thumping
Calm down. Use your MRV missiles first.
Go beyond the vanishing point
I know already!
That reopened wound looks like a beast
Say na na na na, what you say
I'm gonna make you mine, Na!/ Na! Na! Na/
Are you crazy? Never let you go
They dodged the MRVs?/
You got it, never know, in sacrifice
Damn, they can move!
Delta 56/ On your six!
You got it, never know, in sacrifice
Impossible!
(Yes I know, I know)
What the hell is going on? You're right Strong
Fold Wave are emitting from these unknown bogeys!
So crazy, break it down,
break it down, break it down
So crazy, break it down, break it down,
break it down They're some new type of Ghost!
So crazy, break it down,
break it down, break it down
So crazy, break it down, break it down, break it
down G-Ghosts?! Even so, the way they maneuver...
Are you serious? Maybe, maybe...Oh
Sigur Berrentzs main guns at 85%
Just make it a reality
Just make it a reality All fighters
clear the Sigur Berrentzs' line of fire!
All fighters clear the
Sigur Berrentzs' line of fire!
So crazy, crazy, get out! What do you say? All
fighters clear the Sigur Berrentzs' line of fire!
So crazy, crazy, get out! What do you say?
King Heinz!
All hail the King!
So crazy, crazy, get out! What do you say?
So crazy, crazy, get out! What do you say? Energy
charge complete! Line of fire is all clear!
Energy charge complete!
Line of fire is all clear!
! know what you want Energy charge
complete! Line of fire is all clear!
Energy charge complete!
Line of fire is all clear!
You're the only one, take me higher Energy
charge complete! Line of fire is all clear!
You're the only one, take me higher
Fire!
Tell me, what's the meaning
of darkness, darkness?
Tell me, what's the meaning of darkness,
darkness? Enemy flagship main guns firing!
No way out, let me tell you
Raise Dimensional Barrier.
Oh! Oh! Show me the way,
oh no way, no way out
Got 'em!
Shit!
Enemy ship intact.
Presumably preparing
to fire their main cannon.
Sigur Berrentzs, barriers up!
But we don't have enough
power after firing the main guns/
Then there's no choice!
De Enda
De Enda Ulano
Your Majesty!
The Wind Song is too much strain...
De glad a rhyme klan delkez...
De glad a rhyme klan delkez... For His Majesty's
sake, don't let them fire their main gun!
De glad a rhyme klan delkez...
Da/
Le de raam lom
Delta Flight is here to assist!
Klano Klano de aura
Klano Klano de aura - Take this!
- Take this!
Klano Klano de aura
-Those things detached?!
-Spread out!
They're everywhere!
Dammit!
Xao!
Can't hit 'em! Not good...
De Enda
De Enda Ulano
Now.
De glad a rhyme klan—
...All right,
! know you don't look back.
So don't look back
...lom
Klano Klano de aura
De fallo yoo zlam
Tres degna zula
So this is the Singer of the Wind's power...
Del k...
But this ends now.
Are you serious? Maybe, maybe... Of/
Just make it a reality
So crazy crazy, get out! What do you say?
Don't let them through!
Roger/
So crazy crazy, get out! What do you say?
! know what you want
You're the only one, take me higher
Kassim!
Tell me, what's the meaning
of darkness, darkness?
Tell me, what's the meaning of darkness,
darkness? You're not getting though!
No way out, let me tell you
Oh! Oh! Show me the way,
oh no way, no way out What?!
oh no way, no way out
Your Majesty!
They wouldn't!
No way.
They used Reaction warheads in-atmosphere?
These people are crazy!
The Sigur Berrentzs is down...
It'll be okay.
Father Johann,
everyone's safely inside.
Ugh! Father Johann...
Is that it?!
Hayate!
No more!
In a voice tainted with blood, I mustered
my strength and shouted out
Wipe away the darkness of the night/
Siren's Bio-Fold Wave emission
Bitter tears are streamliners,
has dropped to 18%.
About to sparkle and shine
about to sparkle and shine
In reaction to Walkure's song,
Lighting my way, they're on my side it
seems to have entered deep learning mode.
Lighting my way, they're on my side
Lighting my way, they're on my side Just as well,
we've seized control of most of the targeted area.
Study them well and learn their traits.
Misery ongoing.
It still hurts like hell
It still hurts like hell - Their movement's off!
- Now!
I believe in you, it's predetermined
(been there, done that!)
(been there, done that!) They've recovered!
I believe in you, it's predetermined
(been there, done that!)
Over the limit. dash for it
Pulse thumping.
Over the limit, dash for it. Pulse thumping.
Can't keep this up... Something's incoming?
Over the limit. dash for it
Pulse thumping.
Go beyond the vanishing point
Reinforcements?!
That reopened wound
The Macross Gigasion from
That reopened wound Xaos Listania
Branch? What's it doing here?
Xaos Listania Branch?
What's it doing here?
looks like a beast Xaos Listania
Branch? What's it doing here?
looks like a beast
How's a ship that size...
That flying style, is that...?
Gigasion to all fighters.
Get aboard for immediate
withdrawal from Windermere.
But...
Walkire are already being extracted.
Move it/
Copy that.
Think you can keep up, It. Bogue?
What gall!/
Heh, my apologies... We're pulling out!
Commence /landing. Those
heavily damaged go first.
Sorry!
Oh no you don't!
Not good!
I'll get Walkure!
Thanks!
Hayate!
You okay? Hayate! Hayate!
Yeah. Somehow...
King Heinz Nehrich Windermere,
we hereby inform you that
Derwent is now under our control.
If you wish to avoid
further civilian casualties,
you will surrender at once.
How's this? Do you feel
pain anywhere else?
No, but I can't feel my legs...
The attack was so sudden, my men...
Don't give up hope, they
might just be in another room.
Get me the data on treating Windermerians!
How many more wounded are there?!
Delta Flight of Ragna 3rd
Fighter Wing reporting sir.
Captain, we thank you for the rescue.
Can you brief us on the current situation...
He must be this ship's
Zentradi archivist.
Hmm?
Staff Officer Exedol Folmo...
It's been a while, Mirage.
If you're here, that means...
I see you're still leaving your
blind spot wide open, It. Mirage.
That's...
I'm Maximilian Jenius, captain
of the Ma cross Gigasion.
I thought it must be you, grandfather.
Grandfather?
The legendary genius ace pilot.
And captain of Battle 7 of the Ma cross 7 Fleet.
Whoa!
I heard you retired from the military,
Grandfather. What are you doing here?
I was recruited by Xaos.
Rescue orders came from Lady M.
Aren't communications with HQ still out?
The order was transmitted
directly to my brain.
Lady M's Fold comms officer
and I are of the same DNA, so...
Ragna has also fallen to the enemy.
Captain, med bay is reporting that
the Windermerian taken
aboard is in critical condition...
Father Johann!
Apparently he wishes to speak
with It. Hayate Immelmann.
Me?
You are Wright's...
Wright Immelmann's boy, yes?
Your wind is connected
to his, I can feel it.
A wind full of love for freedom
and for the world.
How do you know about my dad?
Your pendant. I was the one
who sent it to your mother.
You? But why?
Well, your father was
stationed on Windermere.
Huh...?
Major Wright Immelmann
was a special operative,
his mission was to investigate
temples and Pro to culture ruins.
A special operative? My dad?
Worry not.
He never did anything to harm our people.
During his mission, something was
taken from a Windermerian temple.
It was a relic of the Pro to culture...
Cell samples of
the Singers of the Stars.
That must be Mikumo's...
The culprit who took them
was a U.N. Government diplomat.
He was really an operative as well.
Wright asked me to help
retrieve the samples...
We were able to recover only one of them.
Then relations between Windermere
and the U.N. Government soured,
making it impossible to return the sample.
Enter Lady M...
I never imagined Major Wright was
involved with the Singer of the Stars.
He went after the other sample,
and it cost him his life...
Your father fought for
Windermere to the very end—
Father Johann!
There is no need to be sad,
I am only fulfilling my duty.
Wright used to say that
all winds will be as one.
We failed to prevent the war,
but someday...
Freyja.
I-I'm here!
A rune that shines too bright
can shorten one's life.
You must reflect on this well.
For what do you live?
For what do you sing...
Father Johann...
Go with the Wind,
to the Fountain of Wind...
Hayate?
A Windermerian becoming one with the wind
is when our time ends.
So you've never seen it before...
The agent who stole the samples
ls currently working for Epsilon.
The Epsilon Foundation, a conglomerate
with thousands of companies to its name.
I've heard plenty of
shady rumors about them.
Sidney Hunt.
It seems he bought himself a fine
position at Epsilon with the sample.
He's the guy behind my dad's...
This man who stole the
other Singer of the Stars'...
That voice we heard
sounded like Mikumo's, but...
There was no soul in it.
It was empty and pitch
black like darkness itself.
A Yamikumo.
Maybe it's not fully-formed.
They might have only made brain
cells and other necessary organs.
But what about that singer we sensed?
A virturoid...
Bio-Fold Waves have the power
to convey music and emotions
through space and time by
resonating with Fold Quartz.
It's very possible that they're using
the Singer of the Stars' power
to boost the energy of their
Reaction Engines and Fold weapons.
You mean they're using music as a weapon?
A video message from Windermere
ls being broadcast on the Galaxy Network.
From Windermere?
- Put it up on the monitor.
- Aye sir.
What's this?
Since ancient times, humanity has made war
throughout history, causing much
death and destruction along the way.
We are Heimdall,
and we are here to liberate
humanity from its rusted chains.
Liberate?
Our objective is to rid the galaxy of
the U.N. Government, N.U.N.S., PMCs,
and the one secretly pulling
all their strings, Lady M.
Lady M is a shadowy figure that has been
manipulating the U.N. Government behind
the scenes, banning the use of advanced
technology and ruling humanity in secret.
Sharon Apple?!
No way!
The ban on A.I. and cloning research, the
restrictions on Pro to culture technology,
all implemented to enforce their
monopoly over advanced technology.
Many tragedies could've been averted if
these had been available to the public,
the Windermerian revolt being one of them.
/It was Lady M who used cell samples
left behind by the Pro to culture
to create the Super Dimensional
Sound Weapon Mikumo Guynemer,
utilizing cloning technology that
was supposed to be banned.
This man...
We cannot tolerate this
oppression any longer.
We shall overthrow these tyrants
and usher the galaxy into a new age/!
Video analysis complete.
Ian Cromwell,
former captain of the Ma cross
Astrea in N.U.N.S.' Seventh Fleet.
He went MIA along with
his ship eight years ago.
So, "Iron" Cromwell is still alive.
He was the hero of the
Battle of Zalg-gantz,
where he subdued
an entire rogue Zentradi
fleet with just one ship.
Why would a hero do this?
That looks like
an advanced model of the illegal
Sharon Apple type quantum A.I. system.
But instead of a bio-neural
chip, they must've
used the Singer of the Stars' cells.
So that's why they took
Windermere and Ragna,
they want to use the Pro to culture
ruins as amplifiers...
If they seize all the ruins in the
Globular Cluster, the galaxy would...
By the order of Lady M,
we are to stop the enemy's plan and
recover the Singer of the Stars' cells.
I wasn't able to handle
the enemy's agility at all.
Will they fly?
Don't worry, we'll patch them up real nice
with spare Kairos parts.
I analyzed the enemy's
Bio-Fold Wave System with
the help of the tech team here,
so we're adding more Fold Quartz
and updating the amplifiers
on each of your Valkyries.
If they can do it, there's
no reason we can't.
The Fold Quartz should react to our music
and boost the Valkyries' performance.
As if we're using our music as a weapon...
That's not true.
He's right. Your music gives us strength.
The strength to protect others.
Music that protects...
Sweet Mira-Mira! You're such a cutie!
T-They're pressing against me!
Not so close!
- Not so close please!
- You're very sweet too, Haya-Haya.
Yeah yeah, okay.
I wonder if Freyja's okay...
To tell the truth, I was a little shocked
seeing Father Johann die.
It really drove home the fact
that we're very different races.
Crystallization... Now that I think of it,
Freyja also showed signs...
That must've just been a side-effect
of the Pro to culture system.
It stopped when the system did...
Yes, I'm probably over thinking things.
Now even you must realize it.
We're different than the Earthlings.
That's...
Our place is within that Wind.
I will take back Windermere,
no matter the cost.
/It seems that Cromwell
has, on many occasions,
petitioned the government to
lift the ban on forbidden technology.
His argument was that the use of unmanned
drones could reduce human casualties,
while cybernetic and cloning technology
could benefit soldiers injured in battle.
Then, during the Battle of Wagenin, he
recommended using MDE warheads
to halt an invasion by a powerful enemy.
He was ignored.
As a result, his fleet and his
home planet were wiped out.
A man like him, having survived
something like that...
He's got nothing left to lose.
There's nothing so dangerous
as a wounded beast.
What about this Heimdall group?
I've heard of it before. People displeased
with Lady M, who operate in secret.
N.U.N.S. still hasn't decided
what to do about them yet.
Approaching destination.
Our makeshift base of operations.
I see. A decommissioned
Zentradi factory satellite...
N.U.N.S. rescue craft?
Survivors from a fleet that ran
into those new enemy fighters.
It. Bogue Con-Vaart here. I'm doing
you a favor and joining Delta Flight.
I'll have you know that I don't
do this kind of service often.
This for real sir?
It's for real.
Now, let's get started.
1,2,3,4,5,6,7,8.
Quit joking around
-Stop it
-Seriously
-No more
-Get lost
Don't treat me like I'm stupid
Wow
You're one to talk
That son of a bitch, you son of a bitch
Just go away already
You dream-stealing rogue
Wow
Hey Miss, those guys are
wolves in sheep's clothing
They're lying in wait, their sights
locked on. Then they swoop in on you
These deluded fools have no shame
These deluded fools have no shame Enemy
combat data uploaded to Super Ghost drones.
These deluded fools have no shame
Reducing limiter by 60%.
They don't even understand heartache
Slippery sun of a...!
Your type of girl? (you fool)
Dammit, can't hit a thing!
Don't make me laugh
They're fast!
See? (See?)
A no good douche bag,
Just like they say
Alright girls, hit it!
So...
Come on women, raise your voices,
make some noise
There's only one truth in this world
Take a look
A maiden's purity is so bewitching,
it'll thrill you and leave you staggering
Thanks, Mirage!
It'll thrill you and leave you staggering
it'll thrill you and leave you staggering
Don't thank me, let's go/
It'll never ever
stand for this
! won't let anyone say
that everything's ruined
! don't care if everything gets messed up
Quit joking around
-Stop it
-Seriously
-No more
-Get lost
Stop treating me like I'm stupid
Wow
We did it...
Wow Not really. These don't
compare to the real thing.
Not really. These don't
Precisely!
AYE-297 Why's there a
blue Durandal out here?
It can't be!
Here I come!
A single
Whoa!
(single)
Voice is small
voice is small
This is bad, we have to sing as one!
So it can be snuffed out
so it can be snuffed out
Copy!
So it can be snuffed out
so it can be snuffed out
Gah! What a wind! But...!
So it can be snuffed out
But if we converge beyond time
(across the sea)
The entire (entire)
Crimson Knight!
Future
future
Outta my way!
Future
future
You get outta mine!
Is ours
is ours
Delta 56 and 6, what are you doing?!
Is ours
So...
I can't keep up with them...
Come on women, raise your voices, make
some noise I can't keep up with them...
Come on women, raise your voices,
make some noise
There's only one truth in this world
Take a look
Ah!
A maiden's purity is so bewitching,
What the hell is this?
It'll thrill you and leave you staggering
it'll thrill you and leave you staggering
He's not like Messer or the White Knight.
It'll thrill you and leave you staggering
it'll thrill you and leave you staggering
I can't read him at all!
It'll never ever
stand for this
Ah, the notorious Immelmann Dance.
! won't let anyone say that everything's
ruined Ah, the notorious Immelmann Dance.
! won't let anyone say
that everything's ruined
! won't let anyone say that everything's
ruined He's got talent, but...!
! don't care if everything gets messed up
Quit joking around
-Stop it
-Seriously
-No more
-Get lost
Don't treat me like I'm stupid
Wow
You're one to talk
That son of a bitch, you son of a bitch
Just go away already
You dream-stealing rogue
Wow
Think I'll call that
the Incredible Dance.
Man, we got beat.
You fly like a pesky insect.
What's that?
I'm on a mission to liberate Windermere,
so don't get in my way again!
So am I!
For your girl?
This isn't a game.
What did you say?
Whoa. C'mon man, don't.
Chuck's family's on Ragna...
and Freyja's village is on Windermere!
What do you care? You're from Earth.
They're an important part of my life now!
So I'm going to take back
Ragna and Windermere!
You're all talk!
What do you plan on doing after you
get them back?! You damn invaders!
Stop this at once!
It. Bogue.
Unlike the Sv-262, the roll rate
of the VF-31 increases as you go.
Practice and get used to that ASAP.
I know.
Hayate Immelmann.
I know how you're feeling,
but you need to have patience.
You two. I wish you had shown
that much spirit on the battlefield.
Grandfather!
Grandpa... Captain are you alright?
You're too kind-hearted
to be a good fighter.
You lack the resolve to go for the Kill
with total disregard for others.
You've probably even disengaged
from a romantic rivalry, for all I know.
T-That's...!
I--.
I don't have your genius, captain.
Yes, you do lack the
talent to be an ace.
Freyja!
Hayate?
Here.
That's... Grandma's apple!
Sorry it took me so long to get it to you.
Thank you Hayate, thank you!
It's pretty bruised up, but
there are seeds inside.
I promise I'll take back Windermere,
then we'll replant the orchard
with these seeds together, okay?
Even if it takes us years...
No, decades.
Okay, Freyja?
Y-Yes... Sure.
Thank you.
Freyja?
Ah, I have to go.
Huh? Hey, Freyja?
You must forgive Hayate.
He's an idiot, but he means well.
Yeah, I know.
But that's the kind of guy
you fell in love with, right?
Yes but... I see now that I'm different,
than you and Hayate.
So you think Hayate won't
be happy if he's with you?
You can't just decide things on your own!
Both of you have to
think this through together!
Alrighty.
I was in love with Hayate too.
Huh?
But I think my feelings for him were
a little bit different than yours.
I guess I admired him.
I wanted to be a free spirit like him.
I'm rooting for you both.
Mirage...
And inter-planetary marriages are
no longer a rare thing these days.
Oh right, Makina told me.
Captain Max was the first one to do it!
M-My grandparents are not
a good example!
Voted No.1 famous couple
most likely to split by the tabloids
for 50 years in a row.
To be fair, the articles said
their problem was more their
personalities than anything else.
Talking romance? We
wanna be in the mix too!
Mixing and churning. Caution, do not mix.
Come on, not again!
I thought I understood
how different our races were, but...
But that doesn't change how
you feel about her right?
No but... I got to thinking,
would she really be
happy being with me?
You two need to talk this through.
If you wait until it's
too late, you'll regret it.
Kaname...
If you half-ass this thing,
you'll have all of Walkire
to deal with. Got it?
Yes ma'am.
I never wanted to be
ship's captain you know.
At the time, N.U.N.S.
was short on officers,
so I had no choice but to accept.
But even now, I still feel I was
born to be a pilot and nothing else.
I'm afraid the same can't
be said for Mirage though.
Yes, she's not really ace pilot material.
Knockout gas?
What are you doing there!
Get down!
Arad!
Commander Arad, are you alright?
Our location's been compromised...
I'm afraid it's worse than that.
My apologies. I was away
from my station when...
No, it's alright.
I'm leaving the team in
your charge, Mirage.
Roger.
A musical score?
It's a directive from Lady M.
Encoded for Xaos' eyes only?
That thing hacked the message, so...
By analyzing the encrypted data,
our enemy must've figured that they
can pinpoint Lady M's location.
Captain Max,
I assume you know Lady M's true identity?
Their official codename is
Lady Megaroad-01.
Megaroad-01... You mean...?
The flagship of the First Emigration
Fleet that left Earth in 2012.
Comms were lost in 2016, and
they've been missing ever since...
Then one of our affiliate organizations
picked up a Fold Wave transmission
coming from subspace
using the same frequency
as the Megaroad-01.
After analyzing the transmission,
we found that it contained the
protocol codes needed to
unlock the mystery of the Star Song
and the Pro to culture ruins.
Then Lady M ls someone
aboard the Megaroad-01?
We don't know.
We're unsure if we can even
call them an intelligent life form.
And you trusted such a thing?
They're not our enemy, at least.
For now.
You don't know that.
If you ask me, this Lady M's
not so different from Cromwell.
The humanoid species of this galaxy
are still too adolescent to handle
the relics of the Pro to culture.
/It would seem that Lady M watches
over civilization, waiting for it to mature.
So we do not make the same mistakes the
Pro to culture made 500,000 years ago.
Have we alerted them?
Yes, but the Megaroad-01 is
caught adrift between Fold Faults
with its systems crippled.
Escape ls impossible.
No...
Are you serious? Maybe, maybe... Of/
Just make it a reality
So crazy, crazy, get out! What do you say?
Fly! With love's (love's)
Kiss (kiss)
! know what you want
I know what you want
Let's link to the end of time
You're the only one, take me higher
Let's link of the end of time
I love you
You're the only one, take me higher
Breaking the limits of passion...
Absolute zero with you
Enemy Bio-Fold Wave Song neutralized.
(Hahn) Advanced Fold Sound
Amplifiers are working!
Delta 4, you've got a squadron of
Ghosts coming in at seven o'clock!
Copy!
Delta 5, keep your focus solely
on the approaching bandits.
Got it/
Delta 3, cover Delta 5's six!
I'll kindle your dreams
Embrace all that you believe
Oorah sir!
Delta 6, bandits three o'clock high!
Embrace all that you believe
Da/
Reckless genes
Almost a lie, heart enflamed to the point of loving
Shake it off
to another dimension, squeeze me
Beating hard,
Cores about to crash (watch me)
Loving the natural you
-Tears
-that can't be shed
-alone
-connect
-our destinies
Fly! Live (infatuatedly)
At the speed (of love)
Super Novatic
Having lost my wings,
I fall
I'm free
They accelerated?!
At last
at last
What the hell is this song?
At last
at last
This evil wind...
Bio-Fold Waves!
Is it multiplying?!
Now I pass
Analyzed... our singing...
Judgement,
It learned from us?
on a self-righteous
Wait, this is...!
On a self-righteous
god
Music is Euphoria.
God
god
Music is Despair.
God
god
Music is Desire.
Music is Insanity.
Music is Darkness.
Die, by the songs of fallen angels.
Super Dark Angels, Yami_Q_ray!
Yami_Q_ray?!
Now entertain me
Seriously?
This world is so boring,
I'm so disillusioned
I'll take everything from you
All your love,
dreams,
music,
and hope
No one will hear you
Power output at 100%.
Come on, break it
The Siren System has awakened.
So it's done.
Come on, break it
Into little pieces. Your body,
your life, your all
Pro to culture structures have appeared
on both Windermere and Ragna!
On both Windermere and Ragna!
I'm not interested in feelings,
on both Windermere and Ragna!
What?!
I'm not interested in feelings,
I'm not interested in feelings, They've
appeared on Voldor and Alfheim as well!
They've appeared on Voldor
and Alfheim as well!
I'll wreck it all They've appeared
on Voldor and Alfheim as well!
I'll wreck it all
I'll wreck it all A Super
Fold Gate is starting to form.
I'll wreck it all
They used deep learning to
It's begun -Destroy- The sound of the end
create copies of the Singer of the Dark,
amplifying their singing power.
Amplifying their singing power.
Has rung out, don't get in my way
amplifying their singing power.
has rung out, don't get in my way Here they
come! All units, engage at close range!
Like an Angel, from the
depths of your D.N.A
Sing devastation, like you're screaming
Evil. Evil. You too are evil. Evil
The hull's been breached!
Shit!
Evil. Evil. You too are evil. Evil
Giving chase!
Deep inside, you must be wishing it too
But deny. Deny. Liar. You still
haven't had enough pain, it seems
Enemy fighters inbound!
Haven't had enough pain, it seems
haven't had enough pain, it seems Do not fall
back! Destroid squadrons, move to intercept!
Do not fall back! Destroid
squadrons, move to intercept!
Perishing is ecstasy
Dammit! Quit buzzing around!
Hayate!
Let's play some more
This isn't nearly enough
They're messing with us!
It's close,
Freyja!
The constellation
that comes but once every 30 years
Freyja!
I don't want to fall asleep
until I see it with you
!/ feel the gears turning
slowly, slowly
What?!
Slowly, slowly
Freyja...
Have you ever wondered how many seconds
Fre-Fre!
No Freyja, don't!
Are in a year,
a day, a moment?
Don't tell me now, I don't even wanna know
when the next comet will come
Don't tell me now, even if this is the end,
That maneuver, what's going on?!
Hayate!
Don't tell me now, even if this is the end,
I don't want to regret it
All forces, evacuate!
The wind starts to blow
without warning
Freyja!
What's happening?
Now!
Don't let me down, tonight
I'll find that constellation
Freyja!
The Ma cross Gigasion has
executed an emergency Fold.
Hmm, seems there's an
issue with the Siren System?
It's not a problem.
We succeeded in generating Bio-Fold
Waves equal to that of all five members
of Walkure combined with the
brain cell count of a single person.
And look,
we've seized all the planets
that have Pro to culture ruins.
Now we can open
Super Fold Gates anywhere in the galaxy.
Funding Roid Brehm's research
has paid off very well indeed.
First you aided the Windermerians,
now you're helping us...
How clever.
Well, you're both our
valued customers.
Enhanced sensory awareness?
Sensing Hayate was in danger,
Freyja's Bio-Fold Waves
intensified to the max.
This caused his Fold Quartz to
resonate with Fre-Fre's singing,
enhancing Haya-Haya's senses and abilities.
So it made him go berserk...
It's my fault... she's like this.
Singing... is... my...
Freyja, I'm taking you off the mission.
No...
Someone who can't even
stand on their own
will be a hindrance on the battlefield.
So you just rest for now.
Relax, we'll take back
Windermere and Ragna.
Then we'll have a party
with jellyfish and apples.
Chuck...
Here, Fre-Fre...
It's a seed from the apple
that Haya-Haya saved.
You should bring it back to Windermere.
Alrighty.
Freyja can't sing anymore?
What do you mean by that?!
You saw how weak she's become...
It's unlikely she can take the strain
of enhanced Bio-Fold Waves anymore...
Can't she be cured?
Crystallization... isn't a disease.
The damage to her cells is severe.
Even if she stops, the
damage has been done...
“A rune that shines too bright
can shorten one's life..."
So this is what Father Johann meant.
The whitening of the body happened
to His Majesty the King as well.
So, if she doesn't sing,
it won't get worse?
I don't know. But she
can't sing on battlefield...
Walkire will do the mission with just
four of you then. It won't be easy...
We'll get the job done.
If we can somehow jam
the enemy's singing...
Let's get started right away.
Okay.
Mikumo?
I... want to sing...!
With Freyja... With you again, Freyja...
Mikumo...
When things got rough during the war,
music helped get me through it.
That's why I always looked up to Walkure.
You protect people with music.
Don't worry. No matter what happens, I'll...
always be a Walkure, okay?
Freyja...
/It's been too long,
Commander-in-Chief Maximilian.
We're all excited to
fight beside you again.
The honor is mine. I'm counting on you.
Commander Arad, what's our plan?
The next time the enemy
opens their Fold gates,
we'll go through one of them
and attack Windermere.
Is that possible?
We've devised a strike plan based
on Commander Arad's proposal.
We believe it to be possible if we
boost the Fold drives of our ships
with Walkure's Bio-Fold Waves.
We believe the gates can be opened on
any planet with Pro to culture ruins.
The nearest one to our
current position is...
Planet Alfheim.
We should be able to sneak in undetected
by using the asteroid belt as cover.
Is there something wrong, Miss Kaname?
No sir.
A fallen comrade used to be stationed on
that planet when he served in N.U.N.S.
It. Messer lhlefeld.
All hands to battle stations/
Repeat, all hands to battle stations/
All hands to battle stations/!
Me? Flight commander?
I can't. We need you to
lead us, Commander Arad!
There's only so much I
can do from the bridge.
It'll be okay. You can do it.
Just be yourself. Fly in your own sky.
Fly... in my own sky...
Hayate.
Sir.
Sorry for not telling you
about your father.
It's alright. But I never would've
guessed he was on Windermere.
I'll tell you more about him some other time.
The kid-friendly stories, at least.
Yes, please do.
Well, don't you have
somewhere to be?
Huh?
Not much time left before the operation.
Yes... Thank you sir.
Freyja...
That darn girl...
Gotta hurry...
Don't be a fool! You're gonna
try to sing?! In your condition?
I'm supposed to be a Walkire!
I'm supposed to be a Walkure, but...
I said, "no matter what happens," but...
Why am I... I'm scared...
I'm afraid to sing.
I'm scared of dying!
I'm supposed to be a Walkure.
A Walkure's supposed to protect everyone by singing.
But I can't... I can't sing.
I'm so scared...
I-I'm afraid I won't be able
to be with you anymore!
Freyja...
What should I do?
What should I do, Hayate?
You have to stop singing.
Then I'll no longer be a Walkure.
Can you live without flying, Hayate?
I'll protect Windermere! I promise.
So I want you to live.
I want you to live on!
I want to live my life with you.
So do I...
I want to be with you too, Hayate.
But...
Freyja!
You and me, I promise...
Fade away in silence
(! prefer being alone)
Darkness is so much
more beautiful than light
So what are you trying to protect?
You're so weak inside, you'll
break into pieces yourself
We're here to free the galaxy
A melody is playing
A melody is playing of Lady M, who
intends to prevent our human civilization,
of Lady M, who intends to
prevent our human civilization,
Listen closely of Lady M, who intends
to prevent our human civilization,
Listen closely
from evolving.
From evolving.
It's inescapable destiny...
from evolving.
The time has come to rise!
It's inescapable destiny...
Deploy all forces!
It's begun -Destroy- The sound of the end
has rung out, don't get in my way
Like an Angel, from the depths of your D.N.A
Sing devastation, like you're screaming
Sing devastation, like you're screaming As expected, acts
of insurrection have broken out within N.U.N.S. ranks.
Sing devastation, like you're screaming
At this rate, it may well lead to
Evil. Evil. You too are evil. Evil
all-out war across the galaxy.
Deep inside, you must already know We'll
take out Cromwell before that happens.
Deep inside, you must already know
Entering Alfheim's defense perimeter.
But deny. Deny. Liar. You still
Commencing Operation Jormungandr!
haven't had enough pain, it seems.
Evil. Evil. I am evil. Evil
-It won't stop,
-the song of fallen angels
-Now all
-will I engulf
-Now all -will I engulf Launch
all assault team fighters!
Launch all assault team fighters!
Come on. A dark and frozen world
You made Mirage flight commander?
! will show you
The abyss
You made Mirage flight commander?
Patience, you'll see.
The abyss
Hayate...
I get it.
There's no way I can fill
Messer's shoes right away.
But still, I want to protect
people like he did.
So doll.
White Knight...
He's just saying we all feel
the same, Crimson Knight!
I received my orders. I'm to be
transferred to the Laramie System.
Oh.
Well that part of the galaxy is still
untouched by the Var Syndrome, it's safe.
So, you're going to be a flight
instructor there. Good luck okay?
Thank you.
It looks like I'll be able to take
my Valkyrie with me.
Although /| doubt we'll see
any more actual combat.
Even so, I'll keep flying Miss Kaname.
Messer...
Then I'll keep singing too.
Messer, guide us.
I could never keep up
You were always
Looking out at something
from this place
Counting those things that,
once possessed,
once possessed, Super Fold
Gate synchronization successful!
Super Fold Gate
synchronization successful!
Are lost Super Fold Gate
Are lost
are lost
All forces, move in!
Are lost
You were hiding your tears,
Fleet course adjustment complete.
Weren't you?
All ships, full speed ahead!
That intense
gaze of yours
Super Fold successful!
Saw the world
Delta Flight, move out!
in a different light
Dreams
Enemy fleet has entered the system.
Aren't reached alone
They've come through the Super Fold Gate!
aren't reached alone
Heh, they're too late!
They fly to us on invisible winds
Perishing is ecstasy
Another gate?!
It seems to be connected to subspace.
Scanning with Fold Radar.
Let's play some more
That's...!
This isn't nearly enough
Wonder if you can reach me
The Megaroad-01!
The time has come!
(Come on, over here)
(Come on, over here) Now we will achieve
what we have fought for all this time!
Now we will achieve what we
have fought for all this time!
Let me see you struggle, hear you wail Now we will
achieve what we have fought for all this time!
Let me see you struggle, hear you wail
Go on, break
The innocent smile of hypocrites
Protect Lady M!
Commence Operation Silence!
ls a sinful dream
is a sinful dream - Roger!
- Oorah sir!
ls a sinful dream
AR
So their strategy is to jam all Fold
Waves, even their own songs.
Fold Jamming successful...
Remember that Walkure's singing will
also lose its effect during jamming.
Let's make this quick!
Delta 5, don't break formation!
Delta 3, the bandit at three o'clock...
No, go with the Thanatos formation!
Get a grip, Mirage!
We'll take them out while
the jamming is effective!
All forces, prepare for
Ma cross Cannon discharge!
All ships commencing transformation.
Connecting power transfer system
Their singing...
I can't hear their singing...
All fighters are to clear the
line of fire immediately.
I repeat, all fighters are to clear
the line of fire immediately.
Energy charge at 130%.
All ships, fire your Ma cross Cannons!
Their barrier's been reinforced.
The jamming system's...
been countered!
So this is the power of the
Siren System. Magnificent!
Walkure is of no further use to us.
Destroy them! Wipe out those
accursed goddesses of Lady M!
(Pouring) You're all slaves now anyway
The Super Fold Gates are reappearing!
(Biting) No use pretending to be cool, no no
no no The Super Fold Gates are reappearing!
(Biting) No use pretending to be cool,
no no no no
(Biting) No use pretending to
be cool, no no no no This angle!
(Lazy) I mean, you're holding it right?
This is bad!
Their line of fire has shifted due to
(Lazy) I mean, you're holding it right?
Windermere's planetary rotation!
An invitation to hell
An invitation to hell If they
fire on the Megaroad-01 with their
If they fire on
the Megaroad-01 with their
(Abashed) It's a dead end, I reckon If
they fire on the Megaroad-01 with their
(Abashed) It's a dead end, I reckon
Hyper Ma cross Cannon from that position...
(Soggy) You're a bunch of riff raft, even standing
still Hyper Ma cross Cannon from that position...
(Soggy) You're a bunch of riff raft,
even standing still
even standing still Windermere will be...
Windermere will be...
(Ouch) In an instant, this world becomes
an indecent prison
But, but, but you
What?!
oblivious to this
oblivious to this Isn't there
some way to stop them from firing?!
Are ecstatic over a fake love The only way
is to destroy the system inside their ship!
Are ecstatic over a fake love
are ecstatic over a fake love
But how?
Are ecstatic over a fake love
are ecstatic over a fake love
With Walkire's singing!
Burn, embrace, cry, regret
That's it! If we boost our
Burn, embrace, cry, regret lil'
Kairos Plus' power with our singing...
lil' Kairos Plus' power
with our singing...
Shatter me, suck on me lil' Kairos
Plus' power with our singing...
Shatter me, suck on me
Shatter me, suck on me It might be able
to break through their dimensional barrier.
It might be able to break through
their dimensional barrier.
Corrupt me It might be able to break
through their dimensional barrier.
Corrupt me
to the very marrow of my bones
Writhe, be paralyzed, be mesmerized, drown
Come to me
Come to me - Reaction warheads!
- Multiple heat signatures incoming!
All forces, intercept incoming
missiles from three o'clock high.
Prevent them from hitting the main fleet!
Roger/
They got though!
We ain't done yet!
Raise Pinpoint Barriers to starboard!
All hands, brace for impact!
So greedy once seduced. How cute
Whew, she's still intact!
ltd be such a bore if everyone
were a hero Whew, she's still intact!
ltd be such a bore if
everyone were a hero
ltd be such a bore if everyone
were a hero Main guns at 75% charge.
ltd be such a bore if
everyone were a hero
everyone were a hero No!
If we don't stop them, Megaroad-01 will...
Yearn, amass, idolize, worship
Lady M will...!
Windermere will...!
Yearn, amass, idolize, worship
Yearn, amass, idolize, worship The
balance of the galaxy will be destroyed!
Burn, embrace, cry, regret
Shatter me, suck on me
corrupt me
Damn you!
To the very marrow of my bones
to the very marrow of my bones
Delta 6, behind you!
To the very marrow of my bones
You thought I was pure, white and clean
Didn't you?
Hayate Immelmann!
That won't do. Pretty flowers are
I vow to defend Windermere!
That won't do. Pretty flowers are The kind people
there, the apple orchards, I'll defend them all!
The kind people there, the apple
orchards, I'll defend them all!
Poisonous, I tell you. (Go mad with wickedness) The kind
people there, the apple orchards, I'll defend them all!
Poisonous, / tell you.
(Go mad with wickedness)
Poisonous, / tell you. (Go mad
with wickedness) And one day, I'll rid
And one day, I'll rid
Dance, night and day. (Go mad
with love) And one day, I'll rid
Dance, night and day.
(Go mad with love)
Dance, night and day. (Go mad
with love) the galaxy of all war!
Dance, night and day.
(Go mad with love)
The poison is potent. (Go mad
with darkness) Then Freyja can
The poison is potent.
(Go mad with darkness)
The poison is potent. (Go mad with
darkness) sing with Walkure again!
Sing with Walkure again!
Sing, night and day. Yeah!
sing with Walkure again!
Haya-Haya...
Sing, night and day. Yeah!
Everyday, tender songs.
Poisonous, I tell you. (Go mad with
wickedness) Everyday, tender songs.
Poisonous, I tell you.
(Go mad with wickedness)
Poisonous, I tell you. (Go mad with
wickedness) Not for stopping wars.
Dance, night and day.
(Go mad with love)
Dance, night and day. (Go mad with
love) And Delta Flight can fly the skies,
And Delta Flight can fly the skies,
The poison is potent I tell you. (Go mad with
darkness) And Delta Flight can fly the skies,
The poison is potent I tell you.
(Go mad with darkness)
The poison is potent I tell you. (Go
mad with darkness) along to their song.
The poison is potent I tell you.
(Go mad with darkness)
(Go mad with darkness) Hayate...
Sing, night and day. Yeah!
We'll live life.
We'll sing together. Fly together.
Detoxification is futile
Detoxification ls futile
We'll live life together!
Detoxification is futile
Hayate...
Both song and wind, together...
Won't give up, won't give up,
Freyja?!
Won't give up,
It's Freyja.
Never ever
Now, now, now,
That voice...
No way...
I can hear someone's voice
- Freyja!
- Fre-Fre!
Freyja, don't!
You've got to stay in bed!
"For what do you live?
For what do you sing..."
I'm sorry, Father Johann.
Sorry, Hayate...
But I'm going to sing.
Because I'm a Walkire!
Freyja, you...
But in your state...
I want to live life,
together with you Kaname!
And Mikumo.
And Makina.
And Reina.
I want to live life
together with everyone.
"Want to live life...
Together...
With everyone"?
To me, living means
singing as a Walkure!
I want to continue living
as a Walkure with you all!
I'm not holding back! Not on life,
not on singing, not on... love.
Not holding back...
I'm gonna live. Live my life to the end.
I wanna be absolutely alive! Absolutely!
Freyja...
I wanna live life together
with you too, Fre-Fre!
Yes. Let's live life, together.
There's no other way. Walkure
absolutely has to be all five of us.
I want to live life too.
Mikumo, Makina, Reina, and Freyja.
I absolutely want to live to the
very end, together with all of you!
Kaname...
Alright! Let's sing!
Our life's song! Absolutely!
Mikumo... You betcha!
For the galaxy.
For someone out there.
We are going to...
Give it all we've got.
Enjoy it as though it's our last!
Go! Walkure!
Won't give up, won't give up,
won't give up,
never ever
No!
Let's live life together, Freyja!
Hayate!
I'll protect you Freyja.
We protect Walkire! That's
what Delta Flight does!
Fly, Hayate! I'll sing!
Now, now, now, [ can hear someone's voice
Songs, songs, songs, I'm guided by the pull
of the stars Winderemere. The apple orchards.
Songs, songs, songs, I'm guided
by the pull of the stars
Songs, songs, songs, I'm guided by the pull of the
stars We're absolutely taking them back ourselves!
Let fly that mysterious sound
(fly to the sky)
Let fly that mysterious sound (fly
to the sky) Delta Flight, let's go!
Let fly that mysterious sound
(fly to the sky)
Let fly that mysterious sound (fly to the sky) - Da!
- Oorah sir!
- Da/
I want to send them to the cosmos (fly to the stars) - Da!
- Oorah sir!
!/ want to send them to the cosmos
(fly to the stars)
A melody that aligns with
the light I yearn for
Yeah yeah yeah
Oh noble heart, let out your birth cry (awaken)
Walkure's Bio-Fold Waves are increasing rapidly.
Oh noble heart, let out your birth cry
(awaken)
Oh noble heart, let out your birth
cry (awaken) So they can still sing.
So they can still sing.
Sing together, amidst changing times
Sing together, amidst changing times Indeed a
formidable musical weapon, chosen by Lady M herself.
Sing together, amidst changing times
It was beneficial that Siren studied them.
A howl! of determination/ Not yet, not yet, not yet,
not yet! It was beneficial that Siren studied them.
A howl! of determination/
Not yet, not yet, not yet, not yet!
Won't give up, won't give an inch,
unfulfilled, love is crying
The virtue of bearing it alone?
Don't need it/
Hearts calling out to each other,
I can see it!
Uniting to unleash a resonating song
uniting to unleash a resonating song
I can see the wind!
Let me feel you deeply, deeply
beyond time and space!
Won't give up, won't give up,
won't give up,
make it better
I want to make it ring out,
ring out, ring out
! want to make it ring out,
ring out, ring out I can't keep up!
I can't keep up!
Endlessly
I can see it!
From here, I can see
everyone's movements.
Delta 5, hard dive.
Delta 6, three o'clock
plus 35 degrees.
Delta 3, ten o'clock
plus 27 degrees, steady.
What?
But there's nothing there...
That's an order! Get ready!
Formation: Midgard!
Roger!
Break me more, feel me more
Target in sight?!
Are you there? Are you out there?
We're right on their tails/
Take this!
Life that blooms on the battlefield,
let it burn, let it burn
End me if my fate is to fade away
Right on, commander!
That was great/!
End me if my fate is to fade away
You read the wind!
Burning, burning, at the end
of destruction You read the wind!
Burning, burning, at the
end of destruction
Burning, burning, at the end of
destruction ... I'm flying my own sky!
...I'm flying my own sky!
Call forth miracles
... I'm flying my own sky!
in the sealed sky
Good going Mirage.
In the sealed sky
in the sealed sky
Gamma Flight to area B7!
I see now, the talent to be a leader.
Love at the limit,
Dangerously border less, it's just insane
Yet I'm still accelerating
Yet I'm still accelerating You're
better suited for the chair than I am.
Yet I'm still accelerating
I'm leaving command to you,
Dancing swiftly,
Captain Arad!
If this is my limit, go ahead and destroy me
I am made from
Max.
I've known you a long time,
destruction and rebirth
destruction and rebirth and I think
this is the best decision you've ever made.
Let's take it to the skies!
Love at the limit,
the forbidden borderline,
no matter the challenge
I'll break through it all
I'll break through it all - What a wind!
- Captain?
- What a wind!
Dancing swiftly, - What a wind!
- Captain?
Dancing swiftly,
I'm no longer captain.
Pulling even more G's, senses are fading
Huh?
pulling even more G's, senses are fading
I'm just a genius!
Pulling even more G's, senses are fading
pulling even more G's, senses are fading
This is...
My body is losing control/
I'm gonna fly away
My body is /losing control I'm gonna fly away
Irregular wave patterns detected in the Siren System!
My body is losing control/
I'm gonna fly away
My body is losing control/ I'm
gonna fly away What is it learning?
My body is losing control/
I'm gonna fly away
My body is losing control/ I'm gonna fly
away Ma cross Cannon power level dropping!
Ma cross Cannon power level dropping!
Reach! With love (lead)
Dance (I'm free!)
I will make adjustments right away.
Fantasy Archrium
Alpha Flight, cover Walkure!
We can do this
When you wake, I'll be by your side, I'll never
let you go again 9 o'clock at 30 degrees, engage!
When you wake, I'll be by your side,
I'll never let you go again
When you wake, I'll be by your
side, I'll never let you go again Da!
When you wake, I'll be by your side,
I'll never let you go again
When you wake, I'll be by your side, I'll never
let you go again White Knight... lend me your wind!
White Knight... lend me your wind!
I swear (Your eyes)
Are dazzling (squall)
White Knight... lend me your wind!
A rush of instinct, a phantom "on” legacy
Silence, an everlasting space
Vacuum Vibe-ray-tion
Understood.
Vacuum Vibe-ray-tion Retrieving the
Singer of the Dark and making my escape—
That was foolish of you...
No one crosses Epsilon and lives...
Die.
Direct all power to
the Ma cross Cannon!
But the ship can't take it!
It might explode upon firing!
It doesn't matter. I'm ordering
all crew to abandon ship.
The Heimdall revolution will live on,
and you will be its driving force!
Ha! Saverg!
Engaging forced energy charge.
God Bless You
[I never knew [/ could love
someone this much
This feeling will never
-be the same again
-God Bless You
The only happiness in a world like this
What a beautiful song.
Freyja...
ls sharing our joy,
the reason for these fears
A wind of life...
So regal...
the reason for these fears
Freyja!
Not yet, not yet, not yet, not yet!
Won't give up, won't give nothing,
ring the bell of hope
We're incomplete if any one of us missing?
That goes without thinking/
Five paths form a five-line staff,
a story to pass down
Carve it into me, blazingly,
blazingly, at the speed of light!
Artificial gravity system damaged'!
Freyja!
Delta 6! Focus on the bandits!
Won't give up, won't give up,
Songs aren't illusions
Music that can connect us is no fantasy
Can you hear this voice?
Are you crying?
Are you laughing?
I'll always be (at your side)
Asking these questions
Close your eyes, listen closely
to your memory of me
Close your eyes, listen closely to
your memory of me Ah, he's improved.
Ah, he's improved.
! want you to always feel me there,
so don't let go/ Ah, he's improved.
so don't let go/
Reach out with both hands and touch me!
See, I'm really warm
Reach out with both hands and touch
me! See, I'm really warm Commander Max!
Reach out with both hands and touch me!
See, I'm really warm
Reach out with both hands and touch me! See, I'm
really warm Go, Immelmann! I've got your back!
Reach out with both hands and touch me!
See, I'm really warm
Reach out with both hands and
touch me! See, I'm really warm Me too!
Me too!
With a shower of words,
And me/
Roger!
With a shower of words,
(Your everything)
I hold you.
Not yet, not yet, not yet,
not yet, not yet, not yet
Not yet, not yet, not yet, not
yet, not yet, not yet Hayate...
Hayate...
Won't give up, won't give an inch,
unfulfilled, love is crying
The virtue of bearing it alone?
Don't need it/
Don't need it/ Not enough power...
The virtue of bearing it alone?
Don't need it/
Don't need it/ Delta 5, take these!/
Hearts calling out to each other,
Ghosts?! Now that's our commander!
uniting to unleash a resonating song
Let me feel you deeply,
deeply, beyond time and space!
Deeply, beyond time and space!
Here we go!
Won't give up, won't give up,
won't give up,
Just wanna...
See it through, see it through,
see it through,
to the very end
Hayate!
Go!
Go get 'em/
Forward!
Just a little more!
"A fruit still green is one
Being attracted is two
My heart is burning”
The sound of singing overlaps
with distant memories
Freyja!
That's...
The song of legend!
The way I'm going and the way I came
There are no mistakes in either
Because I am happy and content (ha-)
Let us sing a song of prayer, that it
reaches the far shores
of this sea of light
A dream to fulfill,
the fire of my life burns
Let us express through music
the joy of being alive
I love you
The words we trade rise to the heavens
A murmured melody
I can hear it! Everyone's singing.
Somewhere deep within me
it becomes a galaxy, eventually
Joy and sorrow
Flowers...
This is...
Joy and sorrow
breathe life into them so they become full
...The legendary...
...Rune Flower...
breathe life into them so they become full
As if in song (ha-)
Let that tender dream
you hold in your heart ring out
Oh my gosh!
You hold in your heart ring out
you hold in your heart ring out
Yami_Q_ray, they're...!
You hold in your heart ring out
you hold in your heart ring out
singing our song!
You hold in your heart ring out
Full of love, my body burns
I commend this warmth
to a new future
Freyja!
To a new future
to a new future
Let's fly together!
To a new future
to a new future - Let's go!
- Let's go!
Let us sing a song of prayer, that it
reaches the far shores
of this sea of light
A dream to fulfill,
the fire of my life burns
A dream to fulfill, the fire
of my life burns To wake...
A dream to fulfill,
the fire of my life burns
A dream to fulfill, the fire
of my life burns he galaxy!
A dream to fulfill,
the fire of my life burns
All ships, fire!
Hayate!
Hayate...
...you hold in your heart ring out
Full of love, my body burns
I commend this warmth
Hayate...
Son of a...
I commend this warmth
to a new future
So, "all winds will be as one."
To a new future
Freyja!
From the bottom of my heart
I love you
- Freyja!
Freyja... Freyja.
Freyja...
Hayate...
So this baby is...
Yeah... a life you saved with your song.
Oh, it's moving.
I don't believe it...
Oh... a rune. It's a rune.
Thank you. Thank you, Hayate.
Yeah... thank you, Freyja.
Your singing felt pretty good.
As always.
Hayate's Immelmann Dance
was... very Gori-Gori too.
Full of love, my body burns
Singing?
Flowers... Everyone's Rune Flowers
I commend this warmth
are blooming.
To a new future
It's so beautiful... looks just
like apple blossoms in bloom.
Yes... so beautiful.
Flowers are white.
Apples are red.
They're sour when they're green.
They're sweet when they're ripe.
Gori-sweet. Gori-tasty.
Yeah, they're Gori-sweet. Gori-tasty.
Mercats are cute.
Jellyfish can glow and float in the sky.
Being alone is lonely.
Being with everyone feels so...
- Fun.
- Warm.
The purple hue of a sunset.
The chirping of birds.
The smell of waking up.
The snowy land.
The wind is gentle.
Singing is fun.
Hayate...
I love you, Hayate.
I love you, Freyja.
Thank you, Fre-Fre...
We'll always be together, absolutely...
That's right, we are Walkure.
We are five and we are one.
Let's continue to sing the song of life.
The words
seeping through my
parched lips
dissipate into thin air
Picking up my broken,
empty shell
It makes me
want to hear your voice
When I look up at the open sky
My legs start
shaking again
Even though I want to believe
that everything in this world has meaning
My mind undecided,
I continue my journey
But this doubt just proves
that I'm still
alive today
Huh Huh Huh
Yeah Yeah Yeah
Yeah Yeah
Huh Huh Huh
Yeah Yeah Yeah
Yeah Yeah
Am I selfish? Am I being naughty?
I just don't wanna lose you
Bit by bit, time is slowly
running out
When you feel like this, hold your chin up
We have to move for war a, right?
I'm ready
Such a pure and crazy BABY
Such an arrogant and obedient BABY
Kinda like the forbidden apple.
Everything's...
OH YEAH
Bold embraces are cool
Great endings are cool
1, 2, 123 GO/
Love can go BAN BAN BA BA BA BAN
and take bloom in a rune
(Hu Huh)
Pouring rains can hug
an entire planet close
WOH WOH WOH (Huh)
Let's go BAN BAN BA BA BA BAN
to nurture this rune and let it bloom
By feeling you there
BAN BAN
Please don't forget
Love can go BAN BAN BA BA BA BAN
and take bloom in a rune (Hu Huh)
Even if it's a dream that will end one day
Doesn't matter,
!/ love you (Huh)
Let's go BAN BAN BA BA BA BAN
to make this rune bloom
in the times to come
Until the day we meet again
BAN BAN BA BA BA BAN
Rune Pika! (Huh)
Flowers are white.
Their scent is mild.
The sun is shiny.
Runes are shiny too.
Hayate flies.
Freyja sings.
I sing too!
Hehe, “I'm comin' right atcha!"